GC2EBJT,2010-08-31T11:32Z,Found it,"I don't ususally get FTF's on a weekday because I still have to work but today I have an 8:00 am dentist appointment so I checked the local caches, and there was one within a mile of my house.  I put the cache into my Delorme and threw my shoes on and was there by 6:32am for the find.  Thank you for putting some so close to home.  There have been a couple in town lately and I really appreciate that.   TNLNSL. TFTC.

[B][blue]javapgmr[/blue][/B]
[B][blue]Columbia, IL[/Blue][/B]
[URL=http://www.geostl.com][B][red]St. Louis Area Geocachers Association(SLAGA)[/red][/B][/URL]
[I]It's not only the destination, but also the path you take and the friends you make along the way.[/I]"
