GC24QFJ,2010-03-29T13:14Z,Found it,"Up to Mark Twain Lake to place the 2010 parking lot caches today and grabbed a bunch of caches while on the way.  This was one of them.  I used to see these kind of things when I drank too much.  Hmmmm.     TNLNSL. TFTC.

[B][blue]javapgmr[/blue][/B]
[B][blue]Columbia, IL[/Blue][/B]
[URL=http://www.geostl.com][B][red]St. Louis Area Geocachers Association(SLAGA)[/red][/B][/URL]
[I]It's not only the destination, but also the path you take and the friends you make along the way.[/I]"
GC25HFX,2010-03-29T15:03Z,Found it,"Up to Mark Twain Lake to place the 2010 parking lot caches today and grabbed a bunch of caches while on the way.  This was one of them.  We ended up on the wrong side of the inlet and had to desend and climb up the other side.  At that point, it was a quick find.  TNLNSL. TFTC.

[B][blue]javapgmr[/blue][/B]
[B][blue]Columbia, IL[/Blue][/B]
[URL=http://www.geostl.com][B][red]St. Louis Area Geocachers Association(SLAGA)[/red][/B][/URL]
[I]It's not only the destination, but also the path you take and the friends you make along the way.[/I]"
