GC24K34,2010-03-27T17:00Z,Found it,"Out caching on a cloudy Saturday morning.  I had cache maintenance to do in the area today so I thought I'd grab a couple close by.  This was one of them. This was a nice quick find.  Glad it got it with no one around today. TNLNSL. TFTC. 

[B][blue]javapgmr[/blue][/B]
[B][blue]Columbia, IL[/Blue][/B]
[URL=http://www.geostl.com][B][red]St. Louis Area Geocachers Association(SLAGA)[/red][/B][/URL]
[I]It's not only the destination, but also the path you take and the friends you make along the way.[/I]"
GC20JR5,2010-03-27T17:37Z,Found it,"Out caching on a cloudy Saturday morning.  I had cache maintenance to do in the area today so I thought I'd grab a couple close by.  This was one of them.  I have some bad news and some good news.  The bad news is that the cache was muggled.  I found both the container and the orange lid thrown under a tree.  I found a couple of trinkets and a broken pen but no log book.  I know it was the cache because the coordinates and name were written on it. I carry supplies and was able to replace the log book and pen. I called someone who knew where the cache was supposed to be  and put it back there.  The good news is that the cache is good to go and ready to be found.  TNLNSL. TFTC. 

[B][blue]javapgmr[/blue][/B]
[B][blue]Columbia, IL[/Blue][/B]
[URL=http://www.geostl.com][B][red]St. Louis Area Geocachers Association(SLAGA)[/red][/B][/URL]
[I]It's not only the destination, but also the path you take and the friends you make along the way.[/I]"
